(birds chirping)
(explosion)
(car sounds)
(clears throat)
(explosion)
Yelp
(shock sound)
(explosion)
Getting closer together.
Is there anyone who can help me?
Inazumax and Smileman are on their way.
Hurry up and set the disaster level!
Yelp
(explosion)
Look! It's a huge explosion!
Damage caused by disaster victims continues to expand on an unprecedented scale.
At present, the level of disaster is being judged on the boundary side... (explosion sound)
- God. -Wait a minute.
(explosion)
Go or (footsteps).
(explosion sound).
(explosion)
(crying)
Dad? Dad!
(laughs)
(explosion)
Nn...
Who are you?
(explosion)
You're a hobby hero. What is it?
The appropriate setting is
I am a vaccine man created by humans repeatedly polluting the environment!
The earth is a living organism.
You humans are nothing but pathogens that will continue to devour life on Earth.
To erase the human race and the foreign civilization it created.
I was made from the stones of the earth!
Is that a hobby?
A hobby?
I mean, (Explosion)
That's why it's human to oppose me!
(explosion)
(explosion sound).
It's over with one pan again.
Damn it!
Music
One Bread!
3,2,1, cunion!
It was the best battlefield victory in history!
Crushing
It won't stop!
One punch!
DONE!
Let's Zero Let's Show!
I'm Cass, Suzuki Cass!
Power Gets Power
I don't want a voice or a cheer that honors me to the limit of my ability.
Hero, so I know how to fight evil! Faye! Faye!
I will not turn my back on an enemy who is pouring in empty weights.
A hero without clothes is a hero who fights accordingly.
The lonely hero.
I am the hero who fights.
Ahhh.
Pooh! Cookckckckckckkkkkkk!
Phantom! Run!
Do you have to run away?
Puff, puff, puff, puff?
Pukupuku - a new salaryman who is tired of the company
I ate too many crabs and suddenly became a pervert.
You have to flee in front of Lord Canilante.
You want to die, don't you?
A different kind of hero, eh?
Hero, I'm not a salaryman, I'm unemployed.
And now I'm looking for a job.
I was interviewed today, but it was beautifully dropped. Why?
It doesn't matter what it is.
When Lord Canilante showed up.
I don't feel like running away.
Pukukuku puku.
Should I run away?
Pukuu
You're as blind as I am.
Yoshimi with dead eyes.
I'm going to let you know that I'm looking for another prey.
a shattered boy on the chin
When I find him, he's on his way.
What are you looking at, bastard?
If he finds it, he'll go first.
Hey, kid, did you do anything to the crab monster?
What?
I slept in the park, so I magically painted my nipples.
This is him, this kid. He doesn't know what he's done.
What do we do? Not yet?
But it's not cute. This has nothing to do with me.
Yeah, it doesn't matter.
Oh, I see. What are you doing?
What?
The kid's after you. Get out of here.
Don't worry about me. Get out of here.
But a football is a ball.
Kuku
What the hell are you doing?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Think about it, you fucker. I've already cut some of them.
Whoever made a fool of this figure is not leaking.
By the way, that kid just fired my body.
And it's oily. I can't even wipe it with a towel.
If you disturb me, I'll make you a body you won't be able to harvest for the rest of your life.
Hahahakuku
I remembered something. You look just like the anime villain you used to see.
Kuku
Die, oh, oh, oh?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Yeah, I wanted to be a hero when I was a kid.
I'm not a salaryman.
He's a hero who can blow a villain like Teme with a single blow.
Don't stop harvesting. Come on. Come on.
You're a hero, you fallen, you're insane. Die here.
Kuku
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Looks like it's been three years since then.
Ever since then, I've been training so hard that I'm so excited.
I've gained unstoppable power.
I wanted to be a hero, but why?
There's something wrong with me. Why am I so unfulfilled? 482 yen. Yes.
Oh, wait a minute.
It is 82 yen.
That's amazing, brother. I can't believe this is so far.
Oh, more than I can imagine, brother.
I wanted to be the strongest man in the world.
The strongest man, that's my dream.
The Ultimate Steroid at Last
Joe Mann, the King of Two Swords is finished.
Brother, if you drink this, you'll have the power you've always wanted.
Do you want to drink this?
Yeah, I made it strawberry-flavored so it's easy to drink, bro.
You can do this with my brain and your muscles.
I wanted the best strength and the strongest body.
If our brothers and sisters join forces,
You can conquer everything on earth and be king. That's great, brother.
Tens of thousands of people are dead. All right, keep cleaning up the town next door.
This is the most powerful force I've ever sought, the emergency evacuation tendency. A giant creature has emerged in the city of D.
A giant creature is approaching City B.
Emergency evacuation. Repeat, City D.
Yeah, let me show you. I'm the strongest man.
What do you think, brother? You're the strongest man I've ever known.
Put on your pants and kill the guy on your shoulder.
Brother, how did this happen? I was just looking for strength.
I've finally become the strongest man.
Look, I don't know who you are, but you killed my brother.
This is the strength of our brothers, I am the strongest, I am the strongest, I am the strongest.
That's why it's empty.
- We're not low.
Automatic power is boring.
The evil in the world never seems to go away.
This is the same as before I started Hero.
I mean, I don't have any influence on society.
I'm not sad about that.
But every day I'm in trouble, my emotions fade away.
I no longer felt fear, tension, joy, or anger.
Have you lost something important in exchange for power?
Previously, there were various emotions swirling in the battle.
If you want to disturb your anger, put on your proud headlights.
Roll lamp
Now it's done in one pan.
Eggs for dinner tonight.
Days to wash gloves back home unscathed.
When fighting monsters and monsters.
There's no soul bumping in there.
I'm just a hero as a hobby.
I mean, if you're satisfied with yourself, that's fine, my blood!
My blood!
[つよい] /strong/robust/
What the hell, guys?
It's rude of you to say that we're real Earthlings, aren't we?
You call us subterraneans.
We decided to take the ground because the numbers were too high.
But it seems that there are quite a lot of people on the ground.
You're going to get in our way.
That's why I'm asking you to go extinct.
Seventy percent of the Grounders have returned to Earth since we began our invasion.
This is also a survival competition. I want you to accept it.
I was surprised, though. I'm the first man on the face of the earth to beat him up and never die.
It's the same here. It's been a long time since I've seen such a resilient phantom.
Underground People
We are Earthlings!
What, what!?
Don't fuck with me!
ACE SPECK:
Damn!
Damn it. We're cooked.
You're done. - What?
Who the hell was that man on the ground?
I'm a hobby hero.
I won't lose, I'll protect the ground!
Sasake! Weak race!
Damn!
Oh, my God, this feeling is the sound of this heartbeat.
This pinch, this tension.
The excitement of this fight!
Yeah, I lost, I remember this!
Oh, my God, my sons are taking such good care of you!
This Underground King will take care of you. This is it!
Sasaki!
&#13;
What I was looking for!
I got it on the ground!
The people on the ground will die!
I am the Underground King! Prepare the ground people!
Come on, let's do it!
I became too strong.
(explosion sound).
Music
Hey, come home early. Sighs shake the crescent moon.
Close your eyes and think about you.
I want to see you, I want to cry, I want to feel romantic.
I've always known this thought, and I've tried so hard.
The people I love are strong, and they're worried about me, but they're weak.
I'll find you before the stars. Come back soon, come back soon (music).
Music
Boo, boo, boo!
How did it go with me this week?
It's time for me, Miss Canilante, to tell you about next week!
So, uh, no footage?
Well, next week a man will appear in Z, where Saitama lives!
What?
Hmm? I don't have time.
Well, for the time being, the next one-pan-man episode 2 "Lonely Cyborg"
Next week, everyone... well, next week.